## **CURRICULUM VITA OF AYANDA FAITH MDUDU**

PERSONAL INFORMATION		
Name	Ayanda Faith Mdudu	
Date of Birth	1996/10/09	
Contact Numbers	0793947402	
Email Address	mduduayanda01@gmail.com	
Address	203 Cook Street, Goodwood, Cape town	
Driver's Licence	Code 8	

## **SUMMARY**

I am Ayanda Mdudu, a full-stack developer with a passion for reading and a deep interest in electrical engineering. I love learning new things and am always committed to finding solutions to every problem. As a hard worker, I believe in persistence and dedication. My skills include proficiency in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, and Python, along with experience in software testing

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND		
Siyahlomula High School	Grade 12 (2014)	
Motheo TVET College	NCV Level 2 (2015) & N4 (2017) Electrical	
	Engineering	
Central University of Technology	Diploma in Engineering Technology Electrical	
	Engineering(2019)	
International Software Testing	Certified Tester Foundation Level (CTFL) v3.1	
Qualifications Board	(2023)	

TECHNICAL SKILLS		
MATLAB	MATLAB OnRamp & MATLAB Simulink	
Arduino Uno	Arduino C Programming	
OrCAD	Pspice	
MPLAB	PIC Assembly Programming	
PowerWorld Simulation tool	Power Stations	
CISCO Networking Academy	Packet Tracer	
Electrical Circuit design	Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint &	
	outlook	
Troubleshooting	V-series, 7000i, and Cobra note sorting	
	machines.	
HTML, CSS, & JAVASCRIPT	Node.js	
React	Python	
Java		

Experience		
Cash Processing Solutions	Field Service Engineer Intern (2020-2021)	
Cash Processing Solutions	Field Service Engineer (2021- 2024)	
Capaciti	ABSA Full stack Developer Intern (2024-	
	currently)	

REFERENCES		
Name: Mrs Mohlaoli	Name: Jaco Van de walt	
Role: Mentor	Institution: Cash Processing Solutions	
Contact Numbers: 0837320721	Role: Reginal Manager	
	Contact Numbers: 0609760597	
Name: Afika Maliwa		
Role: Candidate Success Manager		
contact: afika.maliwa@capaciti.org.za		